<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Empath</string>
    <string name="value_button_start">Start</string>
    <string name="start_text_0">… Hello? Is anyone on?</string>
    <string name="start_option_0">(Keep Waiting)</string>
    <string name="start_option_1">Yeah, I\'m here.</string>
    <string name="choice_1_text_0">You! You’re not supposed to be here yet. Just… stay there. The others will be here soon.</string>
    <string name="choice_1_text_1">…</string>
    <string name="choice_1_text_2">Red? Yellow? Where are you??</string>
    <string name="choice_1_text_3">Chill out, I’m on. I just finished my last character sheet.</string>
    <string name="choice_1_text_4">He’s already here!</string>
    <string name="choice_1_text_5">He? You mean she?</string>
    <string name="choice_1_text_6">Uh, no. I’ve been telling you it’s a he.</string>
    <string name="choice_1_text_7">That’s a straight-up lie! You’ve said she from the beginning!</string>
    <string name="choice_1_text_8">We’re not arguing about this. Please? He’s here and we need to start. Yellow, are you here?</string>
    <string name="choice_1_text_9">Yes.</string>
    <string name="choice_1_text_10">I was also under the assumption that it was a he.</string>
    <string name="choice_1_text_11">See?!</string>
    <string name="choice_1_text_12">But Blue has been calling it a she.</string>
    <string name="choice_text_13">:D</string>
    <string name="choice_1_text_14">Look, let’s just ask. Are you a boy or a girl?</string>
    <string name="choice_1_option_0">I\'m a girl</string>
    <string name="choice_1_option_1">I\'m a boy</string>
    <string name="choice_0_text_0">I love how you guys never take anything seriously. Makes it super fun whenever I plan things like this.</string>
    <string name="choice_0_text_1">Suuuuper fun.</string>
    <string name="choice_0_text_2">Maybe if I specifically tell you to be here at a certain time, then you should be here.</string>
    <string name="choice_0_text_3">I’m here, geez. I was finishing my last character sheet.</string>
    <string name="choice_0_text_4">Also, when have I ever not been serious? I’m Mr. Serious. No smile here. Nada.</string>
    <string name="choice_0_text_5">Whatever, yeah. I just want to go over the plan before he gets here.</string>
    <string name="choice_0_text_6">Wait, he? You definitely said it was going to be a she.</string>
    <string name="choice_0_text_7">Uh, no. He.</string>
    <string name="choice_0_text_8">You’ve been calling her a she this whole time! As in “She won’t know what hit her” and “She’ll be crying herself to sleep after this.” Sound familiar?</string>
    <string name="choice_0_text_9">Okay, it’s possible that those things were said by me. It doesn’t matter.</string>
    <string name="choice_0_text_10">I’ve been picturing a she this whole time :( You’re messing with my vibe.</string>
    <string name="choice_0_text_11">Red, c’mon dude. I need to make sure we’re on the same page with this thing. The plan, not the gender.</string>
    <string name="choice_0_text_12">What about Yellow? We need to wait for her to get on before we start, right?</string>
    <string name="choice_0_text_13">She knows what to do. And she’ll be here.</string>
    <string name="choice_0_text_14">So that whole rant earlier was just directed towards me?</string>
    <string name="choice_0_text_15">Hi, you two.</string>
    <string name="test">Hello</string>
    <string name="hiYellow">Hi, Yellow. For the record, isn’t our guest going to be a he?</string>
    <string name="myUnderstanding">That was my understanding.</string>
    <string name="SHEE">But you have been calling it a she. It’s unclear.</string>
    <string name="ha">HA! I think it’s a she. I’m almost certain.</string>
    <string name="personally">Personally, I imagined it as a he.</string>
    <string name="goodwith">Yeah, yeah, enough about the gender thing. Let’s talk shop. Yellow, are you still good with the Mystic Route?</string>
    <string name="frontof">Blue, should we really be talking about this in front of him?</string>
    <string name="waht">WHAT?</string>
    <string name="yeet">Yes, he’s been here for a minute or so. Sorry, are you a girl or a boy?</string>
    <string name="Girl">Girl.</string>
    <string name="Boy">Boy.</string>
    <string name="agree">Let\'s agree to disagree. The game begins... NOW.</string>
    <string name="personality">Have you ever taken a personality test?</string>
    <string name="lying">Good, you\'re already lying. That\'s an important part of these tests. Just... keep responding naturally.</string>
    <string name="Staycalm">Stay calm.</string>
    <string name="QuestionOne">You cut through the grassy field on your way to class. You\'re in a hurry, so when you spot a flash of white paper amidst the green, you\'ve already taken several steps. Come to think of it, you\'re not sure you saw anything at all.</string>
    <string name="Do">Do you go back and look?</string>
    <string name="Yes">Yes.</string>
    <string name="No">No.</string>
    <string name="Igoback">I go back and look.</string>
    <string name="walking">I continue walking to class.</string>
    <string name="Format">Then you\'re familiar with the format. We\'ll ask you a series of questions. Your answers, your lies, and your false impressions of yourself… they will determine your fate here.</string>
    <string name="different">It\'s a little different than some personality tests.</string>
</resources>
